(Stuart:)I'm jealous.
(Stuart:)Closest I've come
to dating two women
(Stuart:)was that time I dated one woman.
(Leonard:)I don't know how
you put up with it.
(Leonard:)He's impossible.
I mean, holding a meeting
(Leonard:)to decide what
breakfast cereal we should buy.
(Howard:)Yeah. Cap'n Crunch
with Crunch Berries, move on.
(Leonard:)Anyway, Amy, thank you
for sticking up for me.
(Amy:)Oh, I honestly
couldn't care less.
(Leonard:)Sorry?
(Amy:)Well, I just took your side
'cause sometimes I get annoyed
(Amy:)at how close Sheldon
and Penny are.
(Leonard:)Well, they argue all the time.
(Leonard:)They aren't that close.
(Amy:)Who's always comforting
him when he's upset?
(Leonard:)Penny, but...
Who's the only one
(Amy:)who can make him take his
medicine when he's sick?
(Leonard:)I try to hide it
in his peanut butter,
(Leonard:)but he spits it out.
(Raj:)Okay.
(Amy:)And did you know she
has him add things
(Sheldon:)to the Roommate Agreement
so she can get her way
(Amy:)and not fight
with you about it?
(Leonard:)Son of a bitch.